A Guide to Arena Stage Photographs, [1950-1991]
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Guide to Arena Stage Photographs, [1950-1991]
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University University
ARENA 001
7.5 cubic feet
Administrative Information
Access
No restrictions.
Biographical/Historical Information
Arena Stage was an early leader in the resident theater movement. One of the first not-for-profit theaters in the United States as well as a pioneer of the regional theater movement the Arena Stage was the first regional theater to transfer a production to Broadway, the first invited by the U.S. State Department to tour behind the Iron Curtain and the first to receive a Tony Award. Co-founded in 1950 by Edward Mangum a teacher from the George Washington University, and Zelda Fichandler one of his students, Arena Stage was opened in Washington D.C. to fill the void left by the closing of the National Theater in 1948. Deriving it's name from the idea of "theater in the round," Arena Stage became one of the first resident theaters in the United States, beginning with a company of only eight actors. Today, Arena performs to over 250,000 patrons during a September to June season and employs nearly 200 theater professionals and craft persons, who are responsible for all the costumes and scenery seen on stage. Many now- famous actors took part in Arena Stage productions during the early part of their careers. Some of them include Robert Prosky, Morgan Freeman, Dianne Weist, James Earl Jones, Kevin Kline, Christopher Guest, Yeardly Smith and Samuel L. Jackson. Donated to George Mason University in fall of 2000, the Arena Stage Collection contains materials spanning the theater's 50 year history including production notebooks, photographs, playbills, scrapbooks, scripts and handwritten correspondence and other production materials.
Scope and Content Information
Photographs of Arena Stage theater productions, 1950-1991
Arrangement
Alphabetical by production title.
Contents List
- Arena Stage Photographs
  - Abyssinia 1988 - 1989 (Box Box 1)
    Tina Fabrique, Norgen Crayton, Fanni Green, Kimberly Harris, LaDonna Mabry, Mary Bond Davis, David Toney, Rufus Bonds, Jr
  - The Accidental Death of an Anarchist 1983-1984 (Box Box 1)
    Richard Bauer, Raymond Serro, Tom Hewitt, Michael Seter, Susan Plaksin, Michael Jeter,
  - The Adding Machine 1951 (Box Box 1)
    Warner Shreiner, Jacqueline Dudley
  - The Affair 1964 (Box Box 1)
    George Ebeling, Bella Jarrett, Anthony Juke
  - After the Fall 1980 (Box Box 1)
    Linda Lee Johnson, Stanley Anderson, Joanne Hrkach, Inga Bunsch, Halo Wines, Maeve McGuire, Richard Bauer, Mark Hammer
  - Ah, Wilderness 1954 (Box Box 1)
    Gerry Hiken, Lady Astor
  - Ah Wilderness 1979 (Box Box 1)
    Mark Hammer, James Jenner, Barbara Sohmers, Robet Prosky, John Wiley, Annalee Jefferies, Joanne Hrkach
  - Alice in Wonderland 1950 (Box Box 1)
    Lester Rawlins, Marry Mangum, Henry Oliver, Dick O'Neill
  - All My Son's 1954 (Box Box 1)
    Marry Farrel, Lester Rawlins
  - All Summer Long 1953 (Box Box 1)
    George Grizzard, Clay Hall, Marian Reardon
  - All the Kings Men 1987-1988 (Box Box 1)
    Candy Buckley, Stanely Anderson, Walt MacPherson, Ralph Cosham, David Marks, Cassey Biggs, Terry Hinz, Martin Goldsmith, Bob Kirsh, Halo Wines, Henry Strozier, Micheal Hammer,
  - All the Way Home 1963 (Box Box 1)
    Dorothea Hammond
  - American Buffalo 1981 (Box Box 1)
    Kevin Donovan, Mark Hammon, Stanley Anderson,
  - The American Dream 1961 (Box Box 1)
    Anne Chodoff, J. Robert Dietz, Miriam Philips, Stephen Joyce
  - American Splendaor (Box Box 1)
    Fred Strother, Richard Bauer, Anderson Matthews, Brigid Cleary, Isiah Whitlock Jr., Carolyn Swift, Richard Grusin, James C. Nicola
  - An American Tragedy 1979 - 1980 (Box Box 1)
    Ernest Graves, Micheal O'Keefe, Marcia Hyde, Joanne Hrkach, Halo Wines, Annalee Jeferies, Leslie Cass, Debra Monk, Marcia Hyde, Carry Anne Spear, James Jenner
  - Androcles and the Lion 1954 (Box Box 1)
    Gerry Hiken, Bob Blackburn, J. Robert Dietz, Cay Knokey
  - Animal Crackers 1981 - 1982 (Box Box 1)
    Eric Weitz, Karen Jablons, Stephen Mellor, Charles Janasz, J. Fred Shiffman, Donald Corren, Peegy Hewett, Halo Wines
  - Answer the Flute 1957 (Box Box 1)
    Dorothea Jackon Hammond, Sam Robins, Ed Preble, Allen Joseph
  - Arms and the Man 1953 (Box Box 1)
  - The Ascent of Mt. Fugi 1974 - 1975 (Box Box 1)
    Max Wright, Richard Bauer, Mark Hammers, Howard Witt, Dianne Weist, Vivian Nathan
  - As you Like It 1983 - 1984 (Box Box 1)
    Charles Janasz, Christina Moore, Franeer Conroy, Ron Canada, Sheryl Melvin, Terry Hing, William Preston, Kevin Donovan, Marilyn Cosky, Henry Strozier,
  - Awake and Sing 1970 - 1971 (Box Box 1)
  - The Bad Angel 1953 (Box Box 2)
    Lois Bardren, George Gizzard
  - Battle Dreams 1963 (Box Box 2)
    Tony Zerbe, Tom Brannum, George Ebling, Rene' Auberjonoir
  - Bedtime Story 1957 (Box Box 2)
    Del Tenny Ethel Casey, Dick O'Neil
  - Beehive 1986 (Box Box 2)
    Andrea Frierson, Valarie Pettiford, Rozz Morehead, Jodi Socolof, Sherry Hursey, Magda Nova,
  - Beyond Therapy 1983 - 1984 (Box Box 2)
    Halo Wines, Stanley Anderson, Robin Groves, J. Fred Shiffman, Nicholas Wyman,
  - Billy Bishop Goes to War 1980 (Box Box 2)
  - Billy Badd 1965 (Box Box 2)
    Robert Shattel, Alan Oppenheimer, Ted D'Arms, James Kenny, Tom Ligon, Robert Prosky, John Milligan, Richard McKenzie, Robert Stattel, Burke Byrnes, Mel Zimmer, George Ebeling, Tom Ligon, Ned Beatty, Byrne Piven, Antony Zerbe
  - Blithe Spirit 1954 (Box Box 2)
    Marion Reardon, Liselone Christensen, Frances Sternhagen
  - Blithe Spirit 1954 (Box Box 2)
  - Bocioceia? 1974 - 1975 (Box Box 2)
  - Born Guilty (workshop) 1989 - 1990 (Box Box 2)
    Henry Stozier, Pamela Nyberg, Ralph Cosham, Harold Perrineau Jr., Halo Wines, Jhon Leonard Thompson, David Marks, Marissa Copeland,
  - Boy Meets Girl 1955 (Box Box 2)
    Stanley Pitts, Lary Toms, Joseph Gistirak, Jacqueline Dudley, Frances Sternhagen,
  - Briar Patch 1988 - 1989 (Box Box 2)
    David Marks, Marrissa Copeland,Regan Byrne, Beth Hauptle, Bob Kirsh, Sarah C. Marshal, Sandr Bowie, David Marks
  - Brother Pat 1957 (Box Box 2)
  - The Browning Version 1958 (Box Box 2)
    Ethel Casey, Richard Longman, Nicolas Coster
  - The Browning Version 1958 (Box Box 2)
    Richard Longman
  - Buried Child 1982 - 1983 (Box Box 2)
    Stanley Anderson, Christopher Michael, Henry Stozier, Halo Wines, Christina Moore
  - Burning Bright 1951 (Box Box 2)
  - Cabrana 1975 - 1976 (Box Box 2)
  - The Cage 1968 - 1969 (Box Box 2)
    Etnie Allen, Micil Murphy, Rick Cluchey, Randolph Dobbs
  - The Caine Mutiny Court 1960 (Box Box 2)
    Allen Oppenhiemer, Micheal Lipton, Leon Janney,
  - Candide 1982 - 1983 (Box Box 2)
    Marilyn Caskey, Nancy Cameron, Olga Talyn, Paul Binotto, Claudine Cassan, Ivy Austin
  - Catsplay 1976 - 1977 (Box Box 2)
    Helen Burns, Kathrine Squire
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle 1961 (Box Box 2)
    David Hurst
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle 1977 - 1978 (Box Box 2)
    Veroni Castang, Faizul Khan, Robert Prosky, John Wylie
  - Charley's Aunt 1953 (Box Box 2)
    Frances Sternhagen, Richard Sykes, Marion Reardon,George Grizzard, Dick Sykes, Alan Joseph, Gerald Hiken, Stanley Pits, Lois Barden, Penny Young
  - Checkmates 1987 - 1988 (Box Box 2)
    Ruby Dee, Al Freeman, Jr., Elizabeth Van Dyke, Tom W. Jones, II
  - The Cherry Circle 1969 - 1970 (Box Box 2)
    Richard Sanders, Richard Bauer, Michael Lipton, David Darlow, Yusef Bulos, Gloria Maddox, Humphrey Davis, William Hansen
  - The Cherry Orchard 1960 (Box Box 2)
    Anne Diamond, Dorothea Hammond, Norman Barrs, Philip Bosco
  - The Cherry Orchard 1969 - 1970 (Box Box 2)
    Robert Prosky, William Hansen, Phyllis Somerville, David Darlow, Howard Witt, Carol Gustafson, Pamela Dunlap, Gloria Maddox,Grayce Grant, Max Wright
  - The Cherry Orchard 1988 (Box Box 2)
    Shirley Knight, Tana Hicken, Rebecca Ellens, Marrissa Copeland, Mark Hammer, Brian Cousins
  - Children of Darkness 1950 - 1951 (Box Box 2)
  - A Chorus of Disapproval 1988 - 1989 (Box Box 2)
    Beth Howland, Ralph Cosham, Halo Wines, Stanley Anderson, Richard Bauer, Gail Grate, Ann Kittredge, Regan Byrne, Beth Hauptle,
  - Clandestine on the Morning Line 1959 (Box Box 2)
    Joe Runner, Gwyda DonHoweHarry Bergman, Marion Morris
  - Cloud 9 1983 - 1984 (Box Box 2)
    Cherry Jones, Christina Moore, Stephen Mellor, Halo Wines, Kevin Donovan, Tom Hewitt, Mark Hammer, Kevin Donovan
  - The Coconuts 1987 - 1988 (Box Box 2)
    Regan Byrne, Beth Hauptle, Terrence Currier, Ralph Cosham, Stephen Mellor, Mitchell Greenberg, Charles Janasz, Joan Marcus
  - Cold Storage 1980 - 1981 (Box Box 2)
    Robert Prosky, Terrence Currier
  - The Collection 1966 (Box Box 2)
    Janet Sarno, Robert Foxworth
  - The Comedians 1977 - 1978 (Box Box 2)
    Mark Hammer, Andrew Davis, Joel Colodner
  - A Conflict of Interest 1971 - 1972 (Box Box 3)
    Micheal Higgins, Dane Clark, Gleen Taylor, Macon McCalman
  - Conquest of the South Pole 1990 (Box Box 3)
    David Marks, Teagle F. Bougere, Clayton LeBouef, John Leonard Thompson, Margo Hall
  - The Country Girl 1953 (Box Box 3)
    Henry Oliver, Marian Reardon
  - The Country Wife 1953 (Box Box 3)
  - The Cretan Woman 1954 (Box Box 3)
    Lester Rawlins, Marian Reardon
  - The Crucible 1954 (Box Box 3)
    Micheal Higgins, Jerome Kilty, Lester Rawlins, Olive Dunbar
  - Crime and Punishment 1986 - 1987 (Box Box 3)
    Randle Mell, Richard Bauer, Jhon Leonard, Thomas Anthony Quin, Helen Carey, Kate Fuglei, Vivienne Shub, Steven Dawn, Kevin Tighe, Mark Hulswit, Halo Wines, Heather Elhers
  - The Crucible 1986 - 1987 (Box Box 3)
    Stanley Anderson, Randy Danson, Robert Westenberg, Marrissa Copeland, Erika Bogren, Henry Strozier, Halo Wines, Ralph Cosham, Tom Hewitt, Randy Danson, Frances Foster, Heather Ehlers, Lillian Rozin, Kathleen Weber, Richard Dix
  - The Crucible (Israel) 1987 (Box Box 3)
  - Curse of the Starving Class 1978 - 1979 (Box Box 3)
  - Cymbeline 1982 - 1983 (Box Box 3)
    Caris Cofman, Henry Stroizer, Paul Zawadsky, Steven White, Philip Casnoff, Peter Francis-James
  - Dance of Death 1969 - 1970 (Box Box 3)
    Mitchel Ryan, Viveca Lindfors, August Strindberg, Julie Garfield
  - Dandelion Wine 1975 - 1976 (Box Box 3)
    Norman Martin, Micheal Joyce Miller, James Tolkan
  - Dark of the Moon 1952 (Box box 3)
    George Grizzard, Ann Chodoff,
  - Dark of the Moon 1964 (Box Box 3)
  - Death of a Salesman 1974 - 1975 (Box Box 3)
    Bob Prosky, Terry Currier, Stanely Anderson, Bruce Weitz, Dorothea Hammond
  - The Delectable Fudge 1950 (Box Box 3)
  - A Delicate Balance 1981 - 1982 (Box Box 3)
    Myra Carter, Robert Prosky, Barbara Lester, Halo Wines, Mark Hammer, Leslie Cass
  - Design for Living 1979 (Box Box 3)
    Brad O'Hare, Judith Ivey, Jhon Getz, Richard Lupino
  - Desire Under the Elms 1952 (Box Box 3)
    Marian Reardon, George Grizzard
  - The Devils 1963 (Box Box 3)
  - The Devils Disciple 1959 (Box Box 3)
    Philip Bosco, Louis Edmonds, Louise Latham
  - Disability: A Comedy 1981 (Box Box 3)
    Leslie Cass, William Andrews, Charles Janasz, Christina Moore
  - The Disenchanted 1960 (Box Box 3)
    Jim Kelly, Philip Bosco, Alan Oppenhiemer, Ann Meachem, Bob Prosky
  - The Doctors Delima 1957 (Box Box 3)
    Louis Edmonds, Astirid Wilsrud
  - A Doll House 1989 - 1990 (Box Box 3)
    Henry Strozier, Pamela Nyberg, Stanley Anderson, Ralph Cosham
  - Don Juan 1979 (Box Box 3)
    Stanley Anderson, Richard Bauer, Reed Burney, Kathryn Dowling, Jhon Wylie
  - Dream Girl 1957 (Box Box 3)
    Sefton Darr, Margot Hartman, Dick O'Neill, Montrey Mcmurry, Del Tenny
  - Duck Hunting 1977 - 1978 (Box Box 3)
    George Clark Hosmer, Stanley Anderson, Jhon Madden Towey, Clarence Felder, Joanne Hrkach, Halo Wines
  - The Dybbuk 1974 - 1975 (Box Box 3)
    Dianne Weist, Robet Prosky, Howard Witt, Stanley Anderson, Max Wright, Leonardo Cimino, Carl Don
  - Edith Stien 1969 - 1970 (Box Box 3)
    James Luisi, Deryn Warren, Marketa Kimbrell, Ann Meacham
  - The Egg 1960 (Box Box 3)
    Robert Prosky, William Shust
  - Emigre's 1979 - 1980 (Box Box 3)
    Stanley Anderson, Richard Bauer
  - The End of the Beginning: 3 Short Plays 1961 (Box Box 3)
    Bob Prosky
  - Enemies 1972 - 1973 (Box Box 3)
    Gloria Maddox, Dianne Wiest, George Ebeling, Wendell W. Wright, Jr., Leslie Cass, Richard Bauer, Max Wright,
  - Enemy of the People 1975 - 1976 (Box Box 3)
    Bob Prosky, Mark Hammer, Gary Bayer, David Leary,Terrence Currier, Leslie Cass, Howard Witt, Dianne Weist
  - Enrico IV 1988 - 1989 (Box Box 3)
  - Fences 1989 - 1990 (Box Box 3)
    Yaphet Kotto, Kim Hamilton, Wally Taylor,
  - The Firebrand 1950 - 1951 (Box Box 3)
    Gordon Sterne, Angela Nilles, Henry Oliver, Jacqueline Dudley, Lester Rawlins, Pernell Roberts
  - The Flying Karamazov Brothers 1980 - 1981 (Box Box 3)
    Howard Jay Patterson, Paul David Magid, Samuel Ross Williams, Timothy Daniel Furst
  - The Flying Karamzov Brothers 1986 (Box Box 3)
    Randy Neilson, Timothy Furst, Sam Williams, Howard Peterson, Paul Magid
  - The Fool Show 1988 - 1989 (Box Box 3)
    Geoff Hoyle
  - Fools Fire 1984 (Box Box 3)
    Bob Berky, Fred Garbo, Michael Moschen
  - Forever Yours, Marie -Lou 1976 - 1977 (Box Box 3)
    Howard Witt, Laura Esterman, Marilyn McIntyre, Leslie Cass
  - The Foursome 1972 - 1973 (Box Box 3)
  - The Front Page 1958 (Box Box 3)
    Robert Prosky, Robert Brines, Jay Kelly, Jerry Hardin, Charles Egbert, Miller, Harry Bergman, Robert Mareck, Tony Dowling, Gaylord Mason, Jean Schertler, Philip Boscow, Alan Coates, Lyn Alstad, Eugene R Wood, Warner Schreiner
  - Galileo 1964 (Box Box 4)
  - Galileo 1980 (Box Box 4)
    Robert Prosky, Kevin Donovan, Richard Bauer, Terrance Currier, John E Mueller, Halo Wines,
  - The Gangs all Here 1960 (Box Box 4)
    Howard Wierum, Mary Lames, Alan Oppenheimer
  - Gemini 1978 (Box Box 4)
    Bill Randolph, Mel Shrawder, Dick Boccelli, Mel Shrawder, Deborah Baltzell
  - Genesis 1982 - 1983 (Box Box 4)
    Joe Palmieri, Dan Desmond, Linda Lee Jhonson, Joey Ginza, Dan Strickler
  - Gertrude Stien 1980 (Box Box 4)
    Pat Carroll
  - The Girl on the Via Flaminia 1957
    Frances Ingalls, Peter Breck
  - The Glass Menagerie (Box Box 4)
    Jonathan Earl Peck, Ruby Dee, Tonia Rowe, Ken LaRon,
  - The Girl on the Via Flaminia 1957 (Box Box 4)
  - The Glass Menagerie 1951 (Box Box 4)
    Dorothea Jackson, Lester Rawlins
  - Glen Gary Glen Ross 1987 (Box Box 4)
    Robert Westenberg, Ellis Williams, David Proval, Terrence Currier, Henry Trozier, Mark Hammer,
  - Golden Boy 1954 - 1955 (Box Box 4)
    Ann Meacham, Bob Dietz, Dick Sykes, Al Rusico, Alan Oates
  - Good Person of Setzuan 1985 - 1986 (Box Box 4)
    Mark Hammer, Randy DansonJohn Leonard, Thomas Anthony Quinn, Ben Kapen, Rosemary Knower, Tana Hicken
  - Gospel at Colonus 1984 - 1985 (Box Box 4)
    J.D. Steele, Jearlyn Steele-battle, Freederick Steele, Jevetta Steele, Clarence Fountain, Isabelle Monk, Robert Earl Jones, Morgan Freeman
  - The Great Ladies of Blues and Jazz 1987 (Box Box 4)
    Sandra Reaves-Philips
  - Great White Hope 1966 - 1967 (Box Box 4)
    Gil Rogers, James Earl Jones, Jane Alexander, George Matthews, Norma Donaldson, Antonio Fargas, Bill Terry, Jane Alexander, Richard Bauer, Jimmy Pelham, Jane Alexander, Hector Elizando
  - Hamlet 1978 (Box Box 4)
    James David Cromar, Leonardo Cimino, Christine Estabrook, Kristoffer Tabori, Elizabeth Franz, Jhon Gilliss, Arlene Stern, Robert Prosky
  - Happy End 1983 - 1984 (Box Box 4)
    Micheal Genet, Marilyn Caskey, Susan Blommaert, Micheal Cone, Charlie Janasz, Michelle Howard, Casey Biggs, Marilyn Caskey
  - Hasty Heart 1952 (Box Box 4)
    Stanley Pitts, Warner Schreiner, Henry Oliver, Pamela Ritchard, Ed Hall, Stanley Pitts
  - He Who Gets Slapped 1965 (Box Box 4)
  - HeartBreak House 1965 (Box Box 4)
    Kathy Justice, James Kenny, Ted D'Arms
  - Heartbreak House 1975 - 1976 (Box Box 4)
    Barbara Caruso, Jefferey Jones, Jack Ryland, George Bernard, Howard Witt, Robert Pastene, Dianne Wiest, Carolyn Coates, Jeffery Jones, Max Wright
  - A History of American Film 1987 (Box Box 4)
  - The Hollow 1958 (Box Box 4)
    Bronia Stefan, Barbara Lester, Ethel Casey, James Field, Harry Bergman
  - Home 1982 (Box Box 4)
    Samuel L. Jackson, Elain Grahm, Epatha Merkerson
  - Horatio 1973 - 1974 (Box Box 4)
  - The Hostage 1963 1963 (Box Box 4)
  - The Hostage 1963 (Box Box 4)
    Tom Toner, Bella Jarrett, Dee Victor, Alan Oppenheimer
  - The Hostage 1972 - 1973 (Box Box 4)
    Beulah Garrick, Dorothea Hammond, Jay McMillan, Robert Prosky, Gary Bayer, Max Wright, Judith Long, Vladimir Chernozemsky
  - Hotel Paradiso 1963 (Box Box 4)
    Ray Reunhardt, Tom Toner
  - The House of Blue Leaves 1971 - 1972 (Box Box 4)
    Roy Shuman, Leslie CassPhyllis Somerville, Jill Eikenberry, Madelyn Coleman, Grayce Grant, Bruce Kaiden, Dorothea Hammond,
  - The Iceman Cometh 1960 (Box Box 4)
    Jim Kelly, Joyce Ebert, Claudette Nevins, Gaylord Mason, Anne Diamond, Rai Saunders, Harry Hope
  - The Iceman Cometh 1968 (Box Box 4)
    Robert Foxworth, Ned Beatty, Barton Heyman
  - Idiots Delight (Box Box 5)
    Robert Prosky, Halo Wines, Frank Muller, Richard Bauer, John Wylie, Reabecca Beers Street, Gerry Kasarda, Kitty Fitzgibbon, Christina Moore, Lois Hathaway, Annalee Jefferies, Joanne Hrkach
  - The Imaginary Invalid 1982 - 1983 (Box Box 5)
    Richard Bauer, Christina Moore, Halo Wines, Daniel Benzali, J. Fred Shiffman, Marilyn Caskey, Henry Strozier
  - The Immigrant: A Hamilton County Album 1987 (Box Box 5)
    Mark Harelik, Ann Guilbert, Terri Hanauer, Haskell Harelik, Guy Raymond, Ann Guilbert
  - The Importance of Being Ernest 1951 (Box Box 5)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest 1983 - 1984 (Box Box 5)
    Charles Janasz, Richard Bauer, Christina Moore, Tom Hewitt, Marilyn Caskey, Madeleine Le Roux, Mark Hammer
  - In Celebration 1973 - 1974 (Box Box 5)
    Paul Collins, Katherine Squire, Stanley Anderson
  - Indians 1968 - 1967 (Box Box 5)
    Tom Henderson, Micheal Jayston, Raul Julia,Barry Primus, Micil Murphy, Pat Mcdowel, Rick Cluchey, Ernie Alan, Stacy Keach, Manu Tupou, Ed Rombola, Dimitria Arliss
  - Inherit The Wind 1973 - 1974 (Box Box 5)
    Terrence Currier, Robert Prosky, Howard Witt, Max Wright, Dana Eclar, Richard Bauer
  - Jacques Biel is Alive and Doing Well and Living in Paris 1969 (Box Box 5)
  - In the Zone 1961 (Box Box 5)
  - The Inspector General 1951 (Box Box 5)
    Peter Jerome, Henry Daniloxicz, Harry Scully, Henry Oliver, Pernell Roberts, Robert Huey, Barbara Cole, Dick O'Neil, Lester Rawlins, Mary Pray Colin, Henry Lampe
  - The Inspector General 1967 (Box Box 5)
    Jane Alexander
  - Isn't It Romantic 1984 - 1985 (Box Box 5)
    Marilyn Caskey, Lisa Goodman, Scott Wentworth, Janie Blumberg, Halo Wines, Dorothea Hammond, Ben Kapen
  - Joe Turners Come and Gone 1985 - 1986 (Box Box 5)
    August Wilson, Lloyd Richards, Raynor Scheine, Ed Hall, Delroy Lindo, Bo Rucker, Kimberly Scott, Vincent Prevost, L. Scott Caldwell, Mel Winkler, Kippen Hay, LaFontaine Oliver
  - Julius Caesar 1951 (Box Box 5)
    Lester Rawlins, Henry Oliver
  - Julius Caesar 1974 - 1975 (Box Box 5)
    Stanley Anderson, William Newman, David Garrison, Dexter Hamlet, Robert Prosky, Leslie Cass
  - Juno and the Paycock 1957 - 1958 (Box Box 5)
    Margaretta Warwick, Tom Bosley
  - Juno and the Paycock 1990 (Box Box 5)
    Denis Arndt, Jarlath Conroy, Jeffrey Wright, Marissa Copeland, Tana Hicken, Jhon Leonard Thompson, Halo Wines, David Marks
  - K-2 1982 (Box Box 5)
    Stephen McHattie, Stanley Anderson, Regan Byrne, Sara Hope Franks
  - Kean 1981 (Box Box 5)
    Stanley Anderson, Richard Bauer, Halo Wines, Edmund Kean, Mark Hammer
  - King Lear 1969 (Box Box 5)
    Frank Silvia, Ned Beaty
  - Krapp's Last Tape 1961 (Box Box 5)
    Hume Cronyn
  - Lady Precious Stream 1952 - 1953 (Box Box 5)
    Thomas Hill, Marian Reardon, Henry Oliver, Robert Prosky, Goerge Bartenieff, Warner Schreiner, Nicolas Coster, Virgilia Chew, Astrid Wilsrud, Tom Brannum, Philip Bosco, Jeannete Clift, Alan Coates
  - The Last Meeting of the Knights of the White Magnolia 1974 - 1975 (Box Box 5)
    Paul Rudd, Robert Blossom, Patrick Hines, Macon McCalman
  - Ladder to the Moon 1951 (Box Box 5)
  - Leonee and Linda 1973 - 1974 (Box Box 5)
  - Les Blancs 1987 - 1988 (Box Box 5)
    Harold Scott, Mark Hammer, Lilia Skala, Tony Todd, Evelyn Thomas, Basil Wallace, Ralph Cosham, Kaiulani Lee, Richard Beymer, Haimanot Alemu, Lou Ferguson, Jeffery Wright
  - The Lesson 1966 (Box Box 5)
  - A Lesson From Aloes 1981 - 1982 (Box Folder 29)
    Zakes Mokae, Stanley Anderson, Halo Wines
  - The Littlest Circle 1961 - 1962 (Box Box 5)
  - Lonesome Train and Hard Traveling 1965 (Box Box 5)
    Tom Ligon, Richard Mckenzie, Aza Bard, Moses Gunn, Ted D'Arms
  - Long Day's Journey into Night 1975 - 76 (Box Box 5)
    Stanley Anderson, Mark Metcalf, Leora Dana, Mark Metcalf, James Broderick
  - A Look at the Fifties 1972 - 1973 (Box Box 5)
  - Look Back in Anger 1967 (Box Box 5)
    Douglas Rain, Martha Heny, Jane Alexander, Robert Foxworth
  - Loose Ends 1978 - 1979 (Box Box 36)
    Roxanne Hart, Jhon Wylie, Jodi Long, Jay O. Sanders, Celia Weston, Jordan Charney, Kevin Kline, Robin Bartlett
  - The Lower Depths 1976 - 1977 (Box Box 5)
  - A Lie of the Mind 1988 - 1989 (Box Box 5)
    Lily Knight, Micheal O'Hare, David Marks, Halo Wines, John Leonard Thompson, Tana Hicken
  - Light Up the Sky 1987 - 1988 (Box Box 5)
    Tana Hicken, Tom Hewitt, Brigid Clearly, Mark Hammer, Richard Bauer, John Leonard, Ralph Cosham, Cary Anne Spear, Francine Beers
  - Macbeth 1966 (Box Box 5)
  - Mademoiselle Colombe 1958 (Box Box 5)
    Astrid Wilsrud, Sarah Burton, Allen Joseph, Alan Coates, Nicholas Coster, Alan Coates
  - The Madwoman Chaillot 1961 (Box Box 5)
    Kendall Clark, J. Robert Dietz, David Hurst, James Bostain, Robert Prosky, Robert Quarry, Melinda Dillon, Aline MacMahon, Fran Hogau, Brenda Sohick, Stephen Joyce, Gail Ryan
  - The Magistrate 1967 (Box Box 5)
    Robert Prosky
  - Major Barbara 1967 (Box Box 5)
  - Major Barbara 1981 - 1982 (Box Box 5)
    Biff Mcguire, Robert Westenberg, Christine Estabrook, June Hansen, Christopher McHale
  - Major Barbara 1959 (Box Box 5)
    Anne Diamond, Jeannette Clift, Claudette Nevins, Joe Runner
  - The Man Who Came to Dinner 1989 - 1990 (Box Box 5)
    Pamela Nyberg, Tom Hewitt, Richard Bauer, Tana Hicken, Henry Strozier, Nannette Rickert, Halo Wines, Regan Byrne, Sara Hope Franks
  - Man and Superman 1961 (Box Box 6)
  - Man and Superman 1984 - 1985 (Box Box 6)
    Jhon Leonard, Francois de la Giroday, Henry Stozier, Harriet Harris
  - Man of Destiny 1957 (Box Box 6)
  - The Man Who Came to Dinner 1980 - 1981 (Box Box 6)
    Mark Hammer, Annalee Jefferies, Maggie Cutler, Robert W. Westenberg, Kimberly Farr, Sheridan Whiteside, Ernest Graves, Leslie Cass, Christina Moore, Charles Janasz, Richard Bauer, Dorothea Hammond, Terrence Currier, Halo Wines, Robert Prosky
  - Marat Sade 1969 (Box Box 6)
  - The Marriage of Bette and Boo 1980 (Box Box 6)
    Donna Snow, Casey Biggs, Thomas Anthony Quinn, Joe Glenn, Heather Ehlers, Tana Hicken
  - Measure for Measure 1986 (Box Box 6)
    Robert Wetenberg, Ralph Cosham, Richard Bauer, Richard Dix, Kerry Armstrong
  - Merrily We Roll Along 1989 - 1990 (Box Box 6)
    Becky Ann Baker, David Garrison, Victor Garber, Richard Bauer, Marin Mazzie, Melodee Savage
  - A Midsummer Nights Dream 1981 - 1982 (Box Box 6)
    Kathleen Turner, Avery Brooks, Charles Janasz, Avery Brooks, Robert W. Wetenberg, Jhon Madden Towey, Richard Bauer, David Toney, Mark Hammer, Kevin Donovan, Angela Greenwood, Catherine Reinheimer, Tracy Flint
  - A Midsummer Nights Dream 1989 - 1990 (Box Box 5)